collegedegrees.com 2017-12-30

# Privacy Policy - College Degrees

## Terms of Use and Privacy Policy for Use of CollegeDegrees.com (Effective Date 2/5/2016)

Thank you for using the content and services available on CollegeDegrees.com. This document outlines the circumstances governing the use of this website and how CollegeDegrees.com aggregates, and applies those different kinds of information to supply you with content and the associated services and products. By using our website you are agreeing to the following Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. 

Occasionally, we revise our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. We suggest occasionally reading through this document for changes to our policies on privacy and the other concerns stated throughout.

On CollegeDegrees.com two types of information are collected: _submitted information_ and _automatic information_. 

Submitted information includes opting into any web form submission of personal information such as names, telephone numbers, postal addresses and email addresses, which allow us to pair you with the most appropriate education products or services. We store and share that information with schools and third party organizations so they may contact you with information about schools, educational programs and related services. When you submit information, you are authorizing CollegeDegrees.com and affiliated schools and partners to get a hold of you via phone, text message, email and/or mail, in accordance with and applicable laws, in regards to education or related subjects. If you wish to unsubscribe from any email communication, use the link provided in the email to opt-out, at which time you will be removed from the sender’s email communication.

Automatic information is collected anonymously in a fashion similar to that of most websites. This information allows us to make improvements and create user experiences that are as relevant as possible. Using cookies to collect data such as the operating system, IP address, and browser specifications helps us to optimize CollegeDegrees.com, shape our advertising and marketing campaigns, and maintain a database of analytics. For more information please read the _About Cookies_ section below.

By using CollegeDegrees.com, you both recognize and agree that any information collected can be shared with schools, third parties, and affiliated companies to provide you with information about degrees and educational products or services as well as release collected personal data to any company we employ to complete administrative tasks. 

By submitting any personal information to CollegeDegrees.com, you consent to let us and all affiliates, partners, and vendors contact you via text message, phone, email or mail to provide you with information and marketing on educational services and associated products. Moreover, you relinquish any rights afforded to you by the Do No Call requirements set in place by both state and federal governments and provide us an exemption from any other similar laws. You also allow us the lawful right to release your personal information in the case of a subpoena or any other legally required action. This right is only acted upon when CollegeDegrees.com feels it is a necessary act to preserve consumer rights, protect the safety of our users and others, investigate potential fraud, or if CollegeDegrees.com merges with or acquires another company, or if any or all assets are sold to a third party company.

## About Cookies

Cookies are bits of data a website provides to your web browser. Typically, this information is analyzed through Google Analytics, a tool created by Google Inc. We use this information to optimize user experience, as well as to help advertisers reach customers interested in their products. Cookies don’t contain personal information. Third-party or advertising cookies track your navigation online and present ads on behalf of their enterprises.

In depth information about Google Analytics can be found in Google’s privacy policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html.

**We use cookies to:**

  * Collect anonymous demographic information for the purpose of web optimizations.
  * Track how well our marketing converts to engagement and increase its success.
  * Improve ad relevance and user experience

### Refuse and Remove Cookies

If you don’t want to store cookies on your browser, you can remove them at any time. You may have to do it with each use, or you may be able to change your settings to block cookies, depending on your browser.

Also, you can generally opt out of receiving personalized ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or those who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles, as well as from other third party advertisers and ad networks. You may unsubscribe by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.

## Contact Us

Please use our contact form to communicate any comments, questions, or concerns about our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.
